http://highsierramusic.com/privacy

Privacy
High Sierra Music collects personal information when you complete an order and sign up for our eNewsletter. his information is used to complete orders, communicate with customers to provide requested services for issues relating to their order, and send regular eNewsletters with festival updates (from which you have the opportunity to opt-out). High Sierra Music will never ever distribute, sell or otherwise provide any of the personal information that you, our loyal fan, has entrusted us with.
As you browse highsierramusic.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, Gupta, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with highsierramusic.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this page to opt out of Gupta and their partners’ targeted advertising.
We use Google Analytics for aggregated, anonymized website traffic analysis. In order to track your session usage, Google drops a cookie (_ga) with a randomly-generated ClientID in your browser. This ID is anonymized and contains no identifiable information like email, phone number, name, etc. We also send Google your IP Address. We use GA to track aggregated website behavior, such as what pages you looked at, for how long, and so on. This information is important to us for improving the user experience and determining site effectiveness. If you would like to access what browsing information we have – or ask us to delete any GA data – please delete your _ga cookies, reach out to us via this form, and/or install the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On.
How you can access or change your personal information
You can review your personal information and make any necessary changes by logging in to your account here and changing any necessary information. You may contact us here to remove your contact information from our database provided we have completed all pending transactions related to your account.
GET UPDATES ON ALL THINGS HIGH SIERRA!
camping
attractions
bring thefamily
Latest News
Presenting the initial lineup for 2020, with so Read MoreWe’re excited to share that this year’s Silent Read MoreWhat do you do when the Rolling Stones call you to Read MoreIf you have already purchased tickets for Karl Read More
Instagram
Last chance to win Christmas!
Hook up the High Si
Ladies Night!
This weeks Shutterbug Spotlight dip
Cyber Monday Sale!
Get 15% off all week long on o
Remember High Sierra 2010?
